I...
أنا...
Come on.
تعال.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
Not enough.
غير كافٍ.
I'll go to the bathroom first.
سأذهب إلى الحمام أولاً.
Not bad, not bad.
ليس سيئاً، ليس سيئاً.
This game should be played like this.
يجب أن تُلعب هذه اللعبة بهذه الطريقة.
Come on, come on.
هيا، هيا.
Draw cards, draw cards.
اسحب البطاقات، اسحب البطاقات.
Again. I must get the king card.
مرة أخرى. يجب أن أحصل على بطاقة الملك.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Are you shy?
هل أنت خجول؟
No.
لا.
This is
هذا هو
a commemorative necklace of Dream Foundation.
قلادة تذكارية لمؤسسة دريم فاونديشن.
How do you know that?
كيف عرفت ذلك؟
Lan Hewei told me.
أخبرني لان هيوي.
You must take care of Mengmeng.
يجب عليك الاعتناء بمنغمنغ.
I will.
أنا سوف.
She likes orange juice,
إنها تحب عصير البرتقال،
and oranges,
والبرتقال،
and loves watching fireworks.
ويحب مشاهدة الألعاب النارية.
She eats a lot when she's happy,
تأكل كثيراً عندما تكون سعيدة،
and when she's being insincere,
وعندما تكون غير صادقة،
she'll unconsciously smooth her hair.
ستقوم بتمليس شعرها دون وعي.
Her wish
أمنيتها
is to establish an orphan foundation
يتمثل الهدف في إنشاء مؤسسة للأيتام
to help more orphans.
لمساعدة المزيد من الأيتام.
Unfortunately,
للأسف،
I can't be with her anymore.
لا أستطيع البقاء معها بعد الآن.
Then,
ثم،
I'll leave Mengmeng in your care.
سأترك منغمينغ في رعايتك.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
What happened before,
ما حدث سابقاً،
I hurt you.
لقد آذيتك.
I was wrong.
كنت مخطئاً.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Before,
قبل،
you asked me if I could tell who you were.
سألتني إن كان بإمكاني معرفة من أنت.
I know very well.
أعرف ذلك جيداً.
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
Xu Meng,
شو منغ,
I don't expect you to forgive me right away.
لا أتوقع منك أن تسامحني على الفور.
But I beg you to give me a chance
لكنني أتوسل إليك أن تمنحني فرصة
to prove myself.
لأثبت نفسي.
No way.
مستحيل.
There are so many people outside.
هناك الكثير من الناس في الخارج.
No one will come in.
لن يدخل أحد.
Orange flavor.
بنكهة البرتقال.
You like it.
هل أحببت ذلك.
Mr. Yuan. Well.
السيد يوان. حسناً.
Wait a moment. It's a bit noisy here.
انتظر لحظة. المكان صاخب بعض الشيء.
I'll find a quiet place.
سأجد مكاناً هادئاً.
Is anyone inside?
هل يوجد أحد بالداخل؟
Why won't this open?
لماذا لا يفتح هذا؟
That project is like this...
هذا المشروع على هذا النحو...
Well, yesterday,
حسناً، بالأمس،
I contacted them.
لقد اتصلت بهم.
Your staff
موظفوك
is quite dedicated to their work.
إنهم متفانون للغاية في عملهم.
I'm going back.
سأعود.
Someone will come in soon.
سيأتي شخص ما قريباً.
One more kiss.
قبلة أخرى.
Here are your room cards.
هذه بطاقات غرفكم.
Thank you, Mr. Zheng.
شكراً لك يا سيد تشنغ.
Take it.
تفضل.
Yours.
لك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you, Mr. Zheng.
شكراً لك يا سيد تشنغ.
Where's Qing?
أين تشينغ؟
How would I know where he is?
كيف لي أن أعرف مكانه؟
Fine. Good night.
حسنًا. تصبحون على خير.
You live on the second floor.
أنت تسكن في الطابق الثاني.
You've been in the bathroom for so long.
لقد بقيت في الحمام لفترة طويلة.
Don't blame me for not helping you.
لا تلومني لعدم مساعدتي لك.
I can only help you this much.
لا أستطيع مساعدتك إلا بهذا القدر.
Go upstairs.
اصعد إلى الطابق العلوي.
You asked me
سألتني
if I could tell you apart.
لو استطعت التمييز بينكما.
I know very well.
أعرف ذلك جيداً.
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
Xu Meng.
شو منغ.
How could you...
كيف يمكنك...
It must be Zheng Yuanfeng's doing.
لا بد أن يكون هذا من فعل تشنغ يوانفنغ.
You should get some rest.
يجب أن تحصل على بعض الراحة.
The first phase of our project
المرحلة الأولى من مشروعنا
is about to start.
على وشك أن يبدأ.
I will update you
سأوافيك بالتحديثات
on the progress every week.
متابعة التقدم أسبوعياً.
[Mengmeng,]
[منغمينغ]
[are you free tonight?]
هل أنت متفرغ الليلة؟
[I'll take you somewhere.]
سآخذك إلى مكان ما.
It has natural resources,
لديها موارد طبيعية،
but the supporting facilities
لكن المرافق الداعمة
the supporting facilities
المرافق الداعمة
are not enough.
ليست كافية.
We need to
نحن بحاجة إلى
pay more attention to the facilities.
أولوا اهتماماً أكبر للمرافق.
In this way,
وبهذه الطريقة،
we can make the customers satisfied...
بإمكاننا إرضاء العملاء...
I may work overtime.
قد أعمل ساعات إضافية.
I'll tell you when I get off work.
سأخبرك عندما أنتهي من العمل.
And then attract more customers.
ثم اجذب المزيد من العملاء.
We have
لدينا
a certain amount of funds...
مبلغ معين من الأموال...
Mr. Xu. Mr. Xu,
السيد شو. السيد شو،
do you have any additions?
هل لديك أي إضافات؟
Nothing for now.
لا شيء في الوقت الحالي.
[When I was little,]
[عندما كنت صغيراً،]
[my parents often took me to the beach to set off fireworks.]
[كان والداي يصطحباني غالباً إلى الشاطئ لإطلاق الألعاب النارية.]
[That time]
[في ذلك الوقت]
[was the happiest time of my life.]
[كانت أسعد فترة في حياتي.]
[Until]
[حتى]
[Lin Mojiao showed up.]
[ظهرت لين موجياو.]
Dad,
أب،
recharge my phone.
أعد شحن هاتفي.
Didn't your mom teach you
ألم تعلمك والدتك ذلك؟
not to mess with other people's stuff?
عدم العبث بأشياء الآخرين؟
Since you want to see it so badly,
بما أنك ترغب بشدة في رؤيته،
I'll let you see all you want.
سأدعك ترى كل ما تريد.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Dad.
أب.
Who did this?
من فعل هذا؟
Since my brother doesn't want to accept me,
بما أن أخي لا يريد أن يتقبلني،
I'll just go back to the orphanage.
سأعود إلى دار الأيتام.
You little brat.
يا لك من طفل صغير مزعج.
Who taught you to do this?
من علمك أن تفعل هذا؟
How dare you scare your brother with this?
كيف تجرؤ على تخويف أخيك بهذا؟
Is this how we taught you?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي علمناكم بها؟
Dad,
أب،
it's not me.
ليس أنا.
I didn't put that little snake there.
لم أضع تلك الأفعى الصغيرة هناك.
And now you're lying, huh?
والآن أنت تكذب، أليس كذلك؟
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك.
I'll teach you a lesson.
سألقنك درساً.
Huaiwang,
هوايوانج
regardless of who is right or wrong,
بغض النظر عمن هو على حق ومن هو على خطأ،
before the matter is settled,
قبل تسوية الأمر،
how can we just blame the child?
كيف يمكننا إلقاء اللوم على الطفل فقط؟
Look for yourself.
انظر بنفسك.
Mo Jiao made it very clear.
أوضح مو جياو الأمر بشكل جليّ.
Could it be fake?
هل يمكن أن يكون مزيفاً؟
Others may not know Mo Qing,
قد لا يعرف البعض مو تشينغ،
but as his parents,
لكن كما فعل والداه،
don't we know him best?
ألا نعرفه أفضل من غيره؟
You've spoiled him rotten!
لقد دللته كثيراً!
Mo Qing, honey,
مو تشينغ، يا عزيزي،
I believe you. Don't cry.
أصدقك. لا تبكي.
Good boy.
ولد جيد.
I thought
ظننت
he just liked to bully me.
كان يحب فقط أن يتنمر عليّ.
I didn't expect...
لم أتوقع...
Hurry.
عجل.
Hide.
أسرع. اختبئ.
No matter what happens,
بغض النظر عما يحدث،
don't make a sound.
لا تُصدر صوتاً.
Hide.
يخفي.
Hurry.
عجل.
Since you think I'm greedy for the Lin Group,
بما أنك تعتقد أنني طماع في مجموعة لين،
I'll show you.
سأريك.
I'm your mother now.
أنا أمك الآن.
Mother?
الأم؟
You're not.
أنت لست.
You don't deserve it.
أنت لا تستحق ذلك.
[To survive,]
[للبقاء على قيد الحياة،]
[I had to sneak into Country T.]
[كان عليّ التسلل إلى البلد تي.]
[At that time, I swore]
[في ذلك الوقت، أقسمت]
[I would live well.]
[سأعيش حياة طيبة.]
[Even if it takes a thousand times the effort,]
[حتى لو تطلب الأمر ألف ضعف الجهد،]
[I must make Lin Mojiao pay.]
[يجب أن أجعل لين موجياو تدفع الثمن.]
I didn't know you...
لم أكن أعرفك...
Mengmeng,
مرحبًا،
over the years,
على مر السنين،
I've been blinded by hatred,
لقد أعماني الحقد،
and became someone who would do anything,
وأصبح شخصاً يفعل أي شيء،
even lying to you.
بل وحتى الكذب عليك.
I've always lived in darkness and deceit.
لطالما عشت في الظلام والخداع.
It's you who changed me.
أنت من غيرتني.
It was only later that I realized
لم أدرك ذلك إلا لاحقاً
I had fallen for you long ago.
لقد وقعت في حبك منذ زمن بعيد.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
أسرعوا، أسرعوا، أسرعوا!
This is my brother's most important moment!
هذه أهم لحظة في حياة أخي!
Go on. Hurry up.
هيا. أسرع.
Go.
يذهب.
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Oh, no. A patient ran away.
لا، لقد هرب مريض.
Which ward are you from?
من أي حي أنت؟
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
I'll take you back.
سأعيدك إلى هناك.
Ward 16.
الدائرة 16.